I push back against the idea that there's a such thing as someone who is not racist.
Talk about it.
We're either being racist or anti-racist.
If you don't think Donald Trump is racist, that means you believe he's anti-racist.
If he's not anti-racist, then that means he's racist.
Either he's conserving or trying to destroy this structure of racism.
And I don't see any way in which he's trying to destroy it.
But then you also have the folks like Stephen's conception that he's just about his power.
He would then have to say, it's really just those people who are just hateful.
It's not the people who, they may love Black people, but at the same time, if instituting
a policy that harms Black people is beneficial for them maintaining their power, they're
going to do it.
And that person is racist too.
And when we focus on the rhetoric, when we focus on the policies, that's when we can see
whether someone's being racist or anti-racist.
You heard that!
That's the clip.
That was a truth translation, my friend.